<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="story_content">
        <item>
            Python is a widely used
            general-purpose, high level programming language.
            It was created by Guido van Rossum in 1991 and further developed by the Python
            Software Foundation. It was designed with an emphasis on code readability
            and its syntax allows programmers to express their
            concepts in fewer lines of code.
        </item>
        <item>
            A function is a block of organized, reusable code that is used to perform a single, related action. Functions provide
            better modularity for your application
            and a high degree of code reusing.
            As you already know, Python gives you many built-in functions
            like print(), etc. but you can also create your own functions.
            These functions are called user-defined functions.
        </item>
        <item>
            We use open () function in Python to open a file in read or write mode.
            As explained above, open ( ) will return a file object.
            To return a file object we use open() function along with two arguments,
            that accepts file name and the mode, whether to read or write.
            So, the syntax being: open(filename, mode).
            There are three kinds of mode, that Python provides
            and how files can be opened
            "r" for reading.
            "w" for writing.
            "a" for appending.
            "r+" for both reading and writing.
        </item>
        <item>
        According to the structure theorem, any computer program can be written using the basic control structures .
        A control structure (or flow of control) is a block of programming that analyses variables and
        chooses a direction in which to go based on given parameters.
        In simple sentence, a control structure is just a decision
        that the computer makes.
        So, it is the basic decision-making process in programming and
        flow of control determines how a computer program will respond
        when given certain conditions and parameters.
        </item>
    </string-array>
</resources>